EXECUTIVE PROFILE:

4 years 4months of experience in PHP along with database designing.

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS:

Web Technologies: PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, Rest API, JSON.

PHP Frameworks: Laravel, Zend.

Databases Known: MY-SQL.

Tools Known: Eclipse, MySQL Workbench, File zilla, Command Prompt, Composer, SVN

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Company	Duration	Designation	
Aranca pvt ltd.	April 2017 till date	Software Engineer	
Pronto Infotech	Nov 2014 – March 2017	PHP Developer	
Zinc Web Studio	April 2014 – Oct 2014	PHP Developer	

1) Aranca Careers: https://careers.aranca.com/

Team size: 1

Role: Full stack developer

Description: Carrer portal for candidates seeking job in Aranca.

Technology: Zend framework, Mysql, Bootstrap.

2) Opportunities:

Team size: 1

Role: Full stack developer

Description: Intranet portal for internal job positions and referral program.

Technoligies: Core php, Mysql

3) **Bsnl hungama-** bsnl.hungama.com

Project: bsnl.hungama.com is your one-stop entertainment shop. Here you can select and download your favorite music tracks, videos, stream movies and play unlimited online games.

Language & Technology: Prestashop PHP MVC, Smarty, MYSQL, AJAX, CSS, Jquery,

HTML5 Player and Streaming, Rest API.

4) Point Blank: www.pointblankinc.in

Project: Point Blank is a online portal where innovative techno marketing solutions are designed in such a way that brand owners can identify needs of their customers and can fulfil it with personalized effective communications and offers in real time.

Language & Technology: Zend Framework, MYSQL, AJAX, Charts integration, API,CSS, Jquery.

5) **Project Management System:** Intranet project – Aranca.

Project: The flaws in existing system are figured out and a revamped system with new features and solution to existing functional gaps is designed. The usability of application and performance tracking mechanism is improved significantly.

Language & Technology: Zend Framework, MYSQL, AJAX, API,CSS, Jquery, iframe, google charts

6) Proposal Management System:

Project: A portal for creating and managing proposal for clients. Role was to incorporate additional features and change the existing flow of system. Complete redesign of pages was done.

Language & Technology: Zend Framework, MYSQL, AJAX, API,CSS, Jquery, iframe, Jquery, Datatable.

7) Mtnl.hungama.com: http://mtnl.hungama.com

Project: A website for MTNL landline users of Mumbai and Delhi, where customers get access to latest music, videos, movies and games.

Language & Technology: Prestashop PHP MVC, Smarty, MYSQL, AJAX, CSS, Jquery, HTML5 Player and Streaming, Rest API.

8) Graphics portal / Edit portal: Intranet project – Aranca.

Project: Two portals for raising tickets to graphics team and editotial team. Role was to customize existing system.

Language & Technology: PHP, OS ticket platform.

9) Aranca Facility booking: Intranet project – Aranca.

Project: Portal for centralized booking of all meeting/board rooms.

Language & Technology: PHP, Bookedscheduler platform.

10) Other Projects: Record book (Sanghvi Jewellers Kalyan), spicehomejapan.com, virkardevelopers.com, lifefitnessgymkalyan.com.

Professional Achievement:

• **Act now** award Aranca 2017.

Education:

Course	University / Board	Marks Obtained	
B.E. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE	Mumbai	60%	
HSC	Maharashtra	63%	
SSC	Maharashtra	66%	

Personal Details:

Date of Birth	: 20 th April 1989	Marital Status	:	Single
Languages Known	: English, Hindi, and Marathi.	Nationality	:	Indian

Place: Mumbai Signature: _____

Date: (Anil Tyagi)